export const initialData = {
  '1a79eaff26b646e4a108a38894dfc3b6': {
    cards: [
      {
        answer: 'O preço dos computadores baixou recentemente',
        id: '8573792c4eb1439882230eaca334f24a',
        question: 'The price of computers has gone down recently',
        timestamp: 1548023594251
      },
      {
        answer: 'Todos estavam conversando quando o navio começou a afundar.',
        id: '18fc004d1d8d44258a44dbd1a5194523',
        question: 'Everyone was talking when the ship started to go down.',
        timestamp: 1548023582072
      },
      {
        answer: 'Eu gosto de ver o sol se pôr.',
        id: '164931a71e2b478fbf62c10e93bfe0ee',
        question: 'I like to watch the sun go down.',
        timestamp: 1548023569984
      },
      {
        answer:
          'O sistema computacional parou de funcionar por uma hora ontem à noite',
        id: '5835a048fb7b438c98820b1354ece8b2',
        question: 'he computer system went down for an hour last night',
        timestamp: 1548023537397
      },
      {
        answer: 'Ele chegou atrasado para a reunião',
        id: '978329ec06c341119bab532bb4ac8ebe',
        question: 'He showed up late for the meeting',
        timestamp: 1548023526298
      },
      {
        answer: 'Ele tirou a roupa e entrou no banho',
        id: '26f031e25e2c45cd8ce47b5be899a9fb',
        question: 'He took off his clothes and got into the shower',
        timestamp: 1548023508746
      },
      {
        answer: 'O avião decolou no horário certo',
        id: '5bf913a0dd48445699384924af9ce55d',
        question: 'The plane took off on time',
        timestamp: 1548023491911
      },
      {
        answer: 'Eu malho na minha bicicleta ergométrica',
        id: '058520ba0fb54372a45e5df803cfe9c9',
        question: 'I work out on my stationary bike',
        timestamp: 1548023478158
      },
      {
        answer: 'Vou deixar vocês dois resolverem',
        id: '556d7584fd7942cbabce022823981e5f',
        question: 'I’ll let you two work it out',
        timestamp: 1548023454954
      },
      {
        answer: 'Nós precisamos calcular o custo total do projeto',
        id: 'fdaf2a6e2b3b4dcc8169c7591dcea6e5',
        question: 'We need to work out the total cost of the project',
        timestamp: 1548018963738
      }
    ],
    id: '1a79eaff26b646e4a108a38894dfc3b6',
    timestamp: 1547949042269,
    title: 'English Phrasal Verbs',
    maxScore: 80
  },
  '2bb838c3031c4d1a9730be95e7d2277e': {
    cards: [
      {
        answer:
          'Functional programming is an essential concept in JavaScript (one of the two pillars of JavaScript). Several common functional utilities were added to JavaScript in ES5.',
        id: '0f0b21333165411e8d3079b3de009b9f',
        question: 'What is functional programming?',
        timestamp: 1548023761647
      },
      {
        answer:
          'Prototypal Inheritance: instances inherit directly from other objects. Instances are typically instantiated via factory functions or `Object.create()`. Instances may be composed from many different objects, allowing for easy selective inheritance.',
        id: '6f0ac60351774b0a887dbacfa2c7657f',
        question:
          'What is the difference between classical inheritance and prototypal inheritance?',
        timestamp: 1548023751543
      },
      {
        answer: 'It’s an that describes what happened.',
        id: '22f03aa5ddee402b838e17944715de99',
        question: ' What is an Action?',
        timestamp: 1548023733831
      },
      {
        answer:
          'Reducers are pure functions which specify how the application’s state changes in response to an ACTION. ',
        id: '2871df2651504b8f9a45301a73926a82',
        question: 'What are reducers?',
        timestamp: 1548023719054
      },
      {
        answer:
          'A store is a JavaScript which can hold the application’s state and provide a few helper methods to access the state, dispatch actions and register listeners.',
        id: '560361f81fd0405197bd4899a4072675',
        question: 'What is the store?',
        timestamp: 1548023700270
      },
      {
        answer:
          'Predictability of outcome, maintainability, server-side rendering, developer tools, community and ecosystem, ease of testing, organization.',
        id: '514a4985250d4918a3b2d27b942f5aed',
        question: 'What are some advantages of using Redux?',
        timestamp: 1548023681617
      },
      {
        answer:
          'No, it can also be used with other libraries or frameworks like AngularJS, Vue.js, and Meteor.',
        id: 'ceea38ffc0f24296b88cc8ff759017b2',
        question: 'Does Redux only works with React?',
        timestamp: 1548023669802
      }
    ],
    id: '2bb838c3031c4d1a9730be95e7d2277e',
    timestamp: 1548023647028,
    title: 'FrontEnd Questions Interview',
    maxScore: 90
  }
};
